<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talkfunnel Unofficial</string>
    <string name="aboutDNSandDNSSEC">Why does it take some time to propagate your DNS changes? Why did the world move to Ipv6? How to secure your systems from DNS vulnerabilities? By the end of this course, you will have a strong foundation on how DNS works and you can start boring your friends by talking all about it.</string>
    <string name="whyattend">At the end of this course, participants will be familiar with the Domain Name System and Security Extensions to the Domain Name System (DNSSEC). The course is taught “hands-on” in a virtualized FreeBSD environment using the BIND, NSD and Unbound name server implementations. Participants will configure authoritative and recursive domain name servers and will learn to analyse and debug common misconfigurations and bugs. Who knows, this could be your way to a DNS admin job!</string>
    <string name="whoisitfor">Participants should be familiar with Unix-style operating systems. The course is taught on FreeBSD but the environment will be familiar to people with a systems administration background on Linux or Solaris. The virtualized lab environment is hosted on a server in Germany.</string>
    <string name="aboutFossmeet">FOSSMeet is an annual event on Free and Open source software, conducted at National Institute of Technology, Calicut. Started with a vision to create a culture of innovation, evolution and open standards, the meet intends to support the FOSS community and the dissemination of FOSS ideology through hands-on sessions, discussions and lectures. Nothing better to get you introduced to the world of FOSS.</string>
    <string name="aboutPycon">PyCon, the gathering for the community using and developing the open-source Python programming language. This is the first year of the PyCon Pune where the community will meet for two days of talks and working on upstream projects in two days of dev sprint.</string>
    <string name="aboutInstructor">Trouble is an independent consultant and contractor based in Belgium. He provides research and development on low-level software and operating systems, particularly in an embedded or real-time context. His main interests are bootloaders, device drivers and high-performance networking. He can also be convinced to teach courses and workshops on a variety of networking-related topics. In his so-called free time, Philip is a FreeBSD committer contributing mainly to the kernel and a member of the FreeBSD security team. He was one of the main organisers of FOSDEM, the largest annual open source software conference in Europe, from the early 2000s until 2015. He denies having any involvement with amateur radio or tabletop role playing games.</string>
    <string name="aboutJSFOO">JSFoo is India\'s premier JavaScript conference hosted by HasGeek. We launched JSFoo in 2011 as India’s first JavaScript conference. The JS community in India has grown phenomenally since then. JavaScript now pervades every aspect of web development – browsers, apps, front-end, backend, mobile and IoT.
    The broad theme this year is going to be building reliable web apps. Talks will be on these topics and more: tooling and best practices for measuring and monitoring on the web, modern programming languages like ES6/7 and TypeScript, architecture and the practice of programming, specific libraries and frameworks, browser apis like WebRTC, ServiceWorkers, Web Components, Push API, accessibility and localization, game programming, visualisation and animation on the web using javascript.</string>
    >
    <string name="aboutkilter">Kilter is a conference on improving your body via better nutrition, fitness and habits.

    In this first ever edition, the conference will feature talks on data-driven approaches to health and fitness; diets and nutrition; science of food; and food hacking. We are inviting proposals for talks, workshops and demos from researchers and practitioners on these topics.

    Kilter aims to appeal to the widest possible range of individuals who are passionate about and curious to learn how the body works.</string>

    <string name="aboutRootconf">Rootconf is India\'s principal conference where systems and operations engineers share real world knowledge about building reliable systems. We are now accepting submissions for our next edition which will take place in Bangalore on 11-12 May 2017.

    The theme for the 2017 edition is site reliability. The conference will feature talks on state of the art deployment strategies and appropriate monitoring technologies at different scales. Rootconf this year will broadly cover topics like toil, on-call, outage handling, and post-mortem analysis.

    </string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="FACEBOOK_APP_ID">2150654815170532</string>
    <string name="ACCOUNT_KIT_CLIENT_TOKEN">a9c1a26861b706727150b97acabb2886</string>
    <string name="ak_login_protocol_scheme">ak2150654815170532</string>

</resources>
